

ACHMAD FACHRUL

Objective

I am a lifelong learner and highly open to new experiences and i am recently graduated from the Department of informatics and computer engineering, Makassar State University. I prefer to work multi-talented, either on the field or on the front line. I also have proficient skills in processing administrative data using Microsoft Excel.

Education

Makassar State of University

Bachelor's Degree Informatics and Computer Engineering Aug 2016 - Dec 2021

Oct 2019 - Dec 2019

Profile

- Was Born
 Palopo, 22 January 1999
- Gender Male
- Status
 Single
- citizenship
 Indonesia

Skill & Expertise

- Microsoft Office
- Graphic Design
- UI Design
- Web Development
- Creativity
- Communication Skill
- Time Management
- Public Speaking
- Honesty

Contact

089517179488

🔀 achmadfachrul1999@gmail.com

(C) achmadfachrul

in linkedin.com/in/achmad-fachrul

https://achmadfachrul.github.ic

jl. Prumnas antang, Komp.Manggala Permai Blok A/6. Makassar

Work Experience

PT. Telkom Indonesia (Internship)

Indihome technical support

 Working on an indihome network installation project with a team of technicians and doing maintenance

Frontend Web Development (Freelancer)

- Developing web portfolios
- Developing landing page
- Developing company profile

Graphic Design (Freelancer)

- Creating a logo design
- Creating poster design
- Brochure design
- Making business cards

Mar 2021 - Present

Jul 2020 - Present

Organization

Himpunan Pengusaha Muda Indonesia PT UNM

creative economy and telecommunications department staff

Himpunan Mahasiswa Islam Teknik UNM

Youth Department Staff

Himpunan Mahasiswa Elektro UNM

Head of Organizational Development Department

2019 - 2021

2018 - 2019

2017 - 2018